

### HUGO ITURRIETA

### Junior Developer

### **PROFILE**

I'm 23 years old, I'm a proactive person who knows (and loves) teamworking, willing to learn, to work hard and to coolaborate significatively. I consider myself as a nice good guy, that treats people politely. I love programming and I feel that I'm good thinking about solving problems. I love challenges and I'm willing to improve as much as I can

### REFERENCES

#### **Winsor Balderrama**

Ex mission president Facebook | Winsor Balderrama

#### **Bea Stella**

Nursery Department coordinator Cel: +54 291 406-8316

### KNOWLEDGE AND SKILLS

- Front-end: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, JSON, Bootstrap
- Back-end: Python, Java, Ruby. I'm used to OOP. I don't know about databases yet.
- Nice English skills, both speaking and writing/reading.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Stretcher bearer at Hospital Privado del Sur | April 2020 to Present

- Teamwork, time management and responsability.
- Give confidence to patients and transport them around the hospital.
- I learned a lot about medicine(useful as interdisciplinary knowledge).

## Employed at Tiro Paintball | October 2020 to April 2020

- I learned to repair the game guns.
- I had to give safety talks.

### Seller and cooker at "Churros el Topo" | December 2019 to February 2020

- Teamwork and endurance against high pressure
- I was required to move to another city with my coworkers.

# Missionary at "The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints" | May 2017 to May 2019

- Teamwork
- Goal-oriented
- Teaching people and coworkers
- Prepare dialy and weekly reports.

### CONTACT

Phone: 2915132600

Email: hugo.iturrieta@protonmail.com

Address: Bahía Blanca,

Buenos Aires, Argentina



### **EDUCATION**

#### Escuela Técnica N°4

Chemical Technician (2010-2016)

### Universidad del Sur

Systems Engineering (Junio 2019 - Present)

Argentina Programa (guvernamental course) Full-Stack Developer (July 2021 - July 2022)